<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Goals on Keenan Schott</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/tags/goals/</link><description>Recent content in Goals on Keenan Schott</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 12:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.keenanschott.com/tags/goals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A March Update</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/personal/a-march-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/personal/a-march-update/</guid><description>&lt;p>Things never pan out how you think they will.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To be frank, I have put quite a bit of effort into my goals thus far, but I&amp;rsquo;ve had trouble showing for it on this blog. That&amp;rsquo;s not necessarily a bad thing, either. I&amp;rsquo;m doing well in school, on that miserable job search grind, and, interestingly enough, writing a lot. However, none of this writing is available to the public anywhere, and I don&amp;rsquo;t mind keeping it that way.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Skeptic's Resolutions</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/personal/goals-2025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/personal/goals-2025/</guid><description>&lt;p>New Year&amp;rsquo;s Day has come and gone, as has the time to be setting new goals and &lt;a
 href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Year%27s_resolution" rel="external" target="_blank">resolutions&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a>. This year, I intentionally let this day pass me by in an attempt to prove to myself that change can be done at any point in time, irrespective of some convenient window. Okay, maybe I&amp;rsquo;m lying just a little bit - I really did intend to get it together and hit the gym come January, but the easy excuse of having family still in town let me sink deeper into the couch as I let what will almost certainly be my last winter break as a student move on without much of anything being achieved. However, now that I&amp;rsquo;m back in school, I feel the drive to really set some goals and commit to them, hard.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>