<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Keenan Schott</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Keenan Schott</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 12:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Iceland</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/travel/iceland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/travel/iceland/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a
 href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Iceland" rel="external" target="_blank">Iceland&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a> is one of those mysterious corners of the globe to the average American such as myself, which is why I decided to visit with my mother following &lt;a
 href="https://keenanschott.com/posts/education/colorado-school-of-mines/" rel="external" target="_blank">my graduation&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a>. We left on the final day of August on a direct flight from Seattle. Iceland is on &lt;a
 href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Greenwich_Mean_Time" rel="external" target="_blank">Greenwich Mean Time&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a>, meaning an eight hour time difference that did not bode well with my inability to sleep on planes. After we landed at around ten in the morning on the first of September, we picked up our rental car and headed to &lt;a
 href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reykjav%C3%ADk" rel="external" target="_blank">Reykjavík&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a>. Thankfully, Iceland drives on the right side of the road, removing driving as one of the unpredictable variables that comes with travelling abroad. The biggest difference there was how narrow the roads were and kilometers per hour being the standard speed limit format. I would look down at the speedometer, see 100, and freak out for a second.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Arches National Park</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/travel/arches/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 16:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/travel/arches/</guid><description>&lt;p>Wow, time really does fly. I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m only now finding my bearings since my previous post about &lt;a
 href="https://keenanschott.com/posts/travel/mount-lincoln/" rel="external" target="_blank">Mount Lincoln&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a> - I have since moved from &lt;a
 href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Whidbey_Island" rel="external" target="_blank">home&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a> to &lt;a
 href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Edmonds,_Washington" rel="external" target="_blank">Edmonds&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a> to (at some point in the near future) Seattle, visited two national parks, and ventured out of North America for the first time to see the sights in Iceland. As soon as I have the opportunity to organize all my photos, I&amp;rsquo;ll be sure to expand on this post and create future posts on Mount Rainier and the scenes around Reykjavík. In the mean time, in the name of staying on a schedule, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d post this update.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Mt. Lincoln</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/travel/mount-lincoln/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 21:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/travel/mount-lincoln/</guid><description>&lt;p>A staple of Colorado&amp;rsquo;s outdoor culture is undoubtedly hiking &lt;a
 href="https://www.14ers.com/" rel="external" target="_blank">14ers&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a>, or the mountains that exceed 14,000 feet of elevation. Colorado has 53 14ers, California has 12, and Washington has 2 (&lt;a
 href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Rainier" rel="external" target="_blank">Mount Rainier&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a> is definitely on the to-do list). I was approaching the end of my time in Colorado this summer and had yet to hike a 14er, so a buddy of mine and I decided to tackle &lt;a
 href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Lincoln_%28Colorado%29" rel="external" target="_blank">Mount Lincoln&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a>, the 37th highest peak in North America.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Colorado School of Mines</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/education/colorado-school-of-mines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 13:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/education/colorado-school-of-mines/</guid><description>&lt;p>After just over two months since graduating from the &lt;a
 href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7196277618038427648/" rel="external" target="_blank">Colorado School of Mines&lt;i class="fa fa-external-link">&lt;/i>&lt;/a>, I find myself reflecting on my time in Golden. This post focuses exclusively on my academic endeavors, aiming to capture the ways in which I attempted to better myself given that concisely summarizing the entirety of my experiences is an impossible task. I considered discussing the interesting technical knowledge I now have under my belt; not only does that conversation fail to provide a sensible close to this era of my life, but it can&amp;rsquo;t provide you, the reader, with anything worthwhile. Rather, I wish to speak about one class I took at Mines in particular and why I consider it my favorite.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>