<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Keenan Schott</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/</link><description>Recent content on Keenan Schott</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 13:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.keenanschott.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colorado School of Mines</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/education/colorado-school-of-mines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 13:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/education/colorado-school-of-mines/</guid><description>After just over two months since graduating from the Colorado School of Mines, I find myself reflecting on my time in Golden. While there will be a future post dedicated solely to my personal growth and favorite moments during my three years in Colorado, that moment will likely coincide with my departure in August. This post focuses exclusively on my academic endeavors, aiming to capture the ways in which I attempted to better myself. To concisely summarize the entirety of my experiences is an impossible task. I considered discussing the interesting technical knowledge I now have under my belt; not only does that conversation fail to provide a sensible close to this era of my life, but it can&amp;rsquo;t provide you, the reader, with anything worthwhile.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.keenanschott.com/contact/</guid><description>Here are the easiest ways to reach me, listed in order of how quickly you can expect to receive a response:
Email: keenanmschott28 {at} gmail {dot} com School Email: kschott {at} uw {dot} edu LinkedIn DMs: https://www.linkedin.com/in/keenanschott</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.keenanschott.com/about/</guid><description>Hello, and welcome to my website!
My name is Keenan, and I&amp;rsquo;m a recent Colorado School of Mines alum (B.S. in Computer Science with a focus in Computer Engineering, 2024) living in Golden, Colorado. I am a Software Engineer Intern at ICR, Inc. and an incoming student at the University of Washington (M.S. in Information Management with a focus in Program/Product Management &amp;amp; Consulting, 2025). Previously, I worked at Datava.
My technical interests include:
Computer Science &amp;amp; Engineering Full-Stack Development Programming My non-technical interests include:
Music Photography Sports When I&amp;rsquo;m not working or at school, I enjoy skiing, backpacking, and, in general, being outdoors.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/announcements/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:56:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.keenanschott.com/posts/announcements/getting-started/</guid><description>Setting expectations is never easy. Regardless, starting in July, expect new blog posts on the first and fifteenth of every month! I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to blasting my thoughts out into the great abyss.</description></item><item><title>Portfolio</title><link>https://www.keenanschott.com/portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.keenanschott.com/portfolio/</guid><description>Note
This page is my extended Curriculum Vitae containing all of my professional achievements. Fora more concise overview, please view my resume.Education&amp;para;M.S. in Information Management&amp;para;September 2024 - August 2025University of WashingtonI will graduate with a degree in Information Management and a specialization inProgram/Product Management &amp; Consulting (PPMC). I aim to supplement my technical degreeand background with relevant business expertise, and I'm looking forward to moving backto the PNW in August.B.S. in Computer Science&amp;para;August 2021 - May 2024Colorado School of Mines,3.938 GPAI graduated Summa Cum Laude with a degree in Computer Science and a specializationin Computer Engineering from the Colorado School of Mines.</description></item></channel></rss>