<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Portfolios on Keenan Schott</title><link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/</link><description>Recent content in Portfolios on Keenan Schott</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/about/</guid><description>Hello, and welcome to my website!
My name is Keenan, and I&amp;rsquo;m a recent Colorado School of Mines alum (B.S. in Computer Science with a focus in Computer Engineering, 2024) living in Golden, Colorado. I am a Software Engineer Intern at ICR, Inc. and an incoming student at the University of Washington (M.S. in Information Management with a focus in Program/Product Management &amp;amp; Consulting, 2025). Previously, I worked at Datava.
My technical interests include:
Computer Science &amp;amp; Engineering Full-Stack Development Programming My non-technical interests include:
Music Photography Sports When I&amp;rsquo;m not working or at school, I enjoy skiing, backpacking, and, in general, being outdoors.</description></item><item><title>Portfolio</title><link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/stugg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/stugg/</guid><description>Note
This page is my extended Curriculum Vitae containing all of my professional achievements. Fora more concise overview, please view my resume.Education&amp;para;M.S. in Information Management&amp;para;September 2024 - August 2025University of WashingtonI will graduate with a degree in Information Management and a specialization inProgram/Product Management &amp; Consulting (PPMC). I aim to supplement my technical degreeand background with relevant business expertise, and I'm looking forward to moving backto the PNW in August.B.S. in Computer Science&amp;para;August 2021 - May 2024Colorado School of Mines,3.938 GPAI graduated Summa Cum Laude with a degree in Computer Science and a specializationin Computer Engineering from the Colorado School of Mines.</description></item></channel></rss>